<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spatial Computing on Alterscope Solutions LLC</title><link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/tags/spatial-computing/</link><description>Recent content in Spatial Computing on Alterscope Solutions LLC</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:51:09 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alterscopesolutions.com/tags/spatial-computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kanban AR</title><link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/kanban-ar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:51:09 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/kanban-ar/</guid><description>Introducing Kanban AR, the ultimate productivity app that revolutionizes the way you manage tasks and projects! With cutting-edge augmented reality technology, this app brings your kanban board to life, making task management a truly immersive experience…</description></item><item><title>Proximity Sense AR</title><link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/proximity-sense-ar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:20:42 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/proximity-sense-ar/</guid><description>Experience the world in a whole new way with Proximity Sense AR!Our innovative app uses augmented reality technology to sense the distance to objects around you and translate that information into a pattern of vibrations. Simply point your phone in front of you and let the vibrations guide you…</description></item><item><title>Lead the Way</title><link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/lead-the-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:20:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/lead-the-way/</guid><description>Looking for a fun and interactive way to navigate your way to far off or nearby places? Look no further than Lead The Way! With Lead The Way, you can see a virtual sign post right in front of you that points you in the direction of your chosen location and displays the distance to your destination…</description></item><item><title>Self Help Desk</title><link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/self-help-desk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:16:17 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/self-help-desk/</guid><description>What if you could see your situation from a new perspectives? What advice would you give? With this augmented reality simulation, you don’t have to imagine; you can experience. Explore the benefits of a thoughtful and private conversation…</description></item></channel></rss>