<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alterscope Solutions LLC</title>
    <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alterscope Solutions LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 14:12:06 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gradual Nightlight</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/gradual-nightlight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 14:12:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/gradual-nightlight/</guid>
      <description>Transform bedtime for your toddlers with our app! As a parent, I understand the bedtime challenge, which is why I created this app to make it easier for all of us. Use your phone as a reading light during story time and a nightlight for bedtime. What sets our app apart is its gradual screen dimming, ensuring a smooth transition from reading to sleep.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why you&amp;rsquo;ll love our app:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanban AR</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/kanban-ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:51:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/kanban-ar/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Kanban AR, the ultimate productivity app that revolutionizes the way you manage tasks and projects! With cutting-edge augmented reality technology, this app brings your kanban board to life, making task management a truly immersive experience.
Effortlessly organize your workflow and boost your productivity using the power of spatial computing. Visualize your tasks, create boards, and track progress with a simple swipe or a tap. Kanban AR combines the flexibility of a digital platform with the intuitive nature of a physical kanban board, giving you the best of both worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Trend Tracker</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/simple-trend-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 23:10:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/simple-trend-tracker/</guid>
      <description>Easily record the numbers that matter to you and quickly spot trends over time. Our app allows you to track data, such as calories, minutes of activity, hours with a client, and much more. And the values are easy to see on a dynamically updating chart. Download now and gain insight into your life!
Now available on the App Store!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iSwear Jar</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/iswear-jar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:44:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/iswear-jar/</guid>
      <description>The iSwear Jar gives you the power to create or destroy any habit. Simply imagine a dollar bill being thinly sliced by a paper shredder, turning cool cash into green slivers&amp;hellip; Then imagine that dollar bill was yours, and that you surrendered it as a penalty for slipping up. This technique of using a freely made decision to bind oneself in the future is called a Ulysses Pact, and dates back to the Odyssey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:22:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/support/</guid>
      <description> Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:22:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Alterscope Solutions was founded by Matt in 2021 to bring new ideas to life and to try to improve the daily lives of a large number of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:21:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Information Collection, Use, and Sharing: The content of your sessions within Alterscope Solutions software (i.e. microphone data, positional/rotational data, and/or camera data) reside only on your local device. A temporary copy of the data is stored only when Alterscope Solutions software is in use, and it is destroyed when you exit Alterscope Solutions software.
We will not sell or rent any information collected through the use of Alterscope Solutions software or website to anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proximity Sense AR</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/proximity-sense-ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:20:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/proximity-sense-ar/</guid>
      <description>Experience the world in a whole new way with Proximity Sense AR!
Our innovative app uses augmented reality technology to sense the distance to objects around you and translate that information into a pattern of vibrations. Simply point your phone in front of you and let the vibrations guide you. The closer you get to an object, the more intense the vibrations become.
Proximity Sense AR is perfect for exploring an environment by touch alone, and if your device has a LIDAR sensor, it can even be used to navigate in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead the Way</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/lead-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:20:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/lead-the-way/</guid>
      <description>Looking for a fun and interactive way to navigate your way to far off or nearby places? Look no further than Lead The Way!
With Lead The Way, you can see a virtual sign post right in front of you that points you in the direction of your chosen location and displays the distance to your destination. Simply enter your own custom locations, and watch as the sign post appears in your real-world environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gamma 40 Hertz</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/gamma-40-hertz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:19:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/gamma-40-hertz/</guid>
      <description>The Gamma 40 Hertz app gives you access to a quick brain boost. Some recent research suggests that 40 hertz gamma brain waves decline with age and that reversing the decline can be helpful. This app stimulates 40 hertz gamma waves through light, sound, and touch.
Features:
Multimodal, individually adjustable intensity across sound, touch, and sight 40 hertz square wave audio tone 40 hertz haptic vibration 40 hertz visual signal using your device’s flash Now available on the App Store!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purrfect App</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/purrfect-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:18:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/purrfect-app/</guid>
      <description>The Purrfect App will bring you instant relaxation using your phone’s vibration motor to simulate a purring cat. Sit back, relax, and enjoy a gentle purr.
Available on the App Store!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Um Detector</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/the-um-detector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:17:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/the-um-detector/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to improve your speaking? Do find yourself yourself overusing filler words? This app will help you break the habit and speak more confidently.
The Um Detector listens for when you say any these words and/or phrases: “um,” “like,” and “you know.” When it detects a filler word being used, the word will flash red, and optionally, your device will vibrate.
The free version of this app allows you to use it for 5 minutes per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Help Desk</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/self-help-desk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:16:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/self-help-desk/</guid>
      <description>What if you could see your situation from a new perspectives? What advice would you give? With this augmented reality simulation, you don’t have to imagine; you can experience.
Explore the benefits of a thoughtful and private conversation with a close ally: yourself. Continue the conversation through as many rounds a you like, swapping perspectives each time. You can even take a completely new perspective by replaying the conversation from a third person point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Alterscope</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/the-alterscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:10:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/the-alterscope/</guid>
      <description>In this simulation, you begin by selecting a conversation partner. The conversation starts when you record a question or statement. You are then transported into the perspective of your conversation partner, where you can listen and respond to what was said. Continue the conversation through as many rounds a you like, swapping perspectives each time. You can even take on a completely new perspective by observing the conversation from a third person point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
