<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self Improvement on Alterscope Solutions LLC</title>
    <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/tags/self-improvement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self Improvement on Alterscope Solutions LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 23:10:34 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alterscopesolutions.com/tags/self-improvement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simple Trend Tracker</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/simple-trend-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 23:10:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/simple-trend-tracker/</guid>
      <description>Easily record the numbers that matter to you and quickly spot trends over time. Our app allows you to track data, such as calories, minutes of activity, hours with a client, and much more. And the values are easy to see on a dynamically updating chart. Download now and gain insight into your life!
Now available on the App Store!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iSwear Jar</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/iswear-jar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:44:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/iswear-jar/</guid>
      <description>The iSwear Jar gives you the power to create or destroy any habit. Simply imagine a dollar bill being thinly sliced by a paper shredder, turning cool cash into green slivers&amp;hellip; Then imagine that dollar bill was yours, and that you surrendered it as a penalty for slipping up. This technique of using a freely made decision to bind oneself in the future is called a Ulysses Pact, and dates back to the Odyssey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gamma 40 Hertz</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/gamma-40-hertz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:19:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/gamma-40-hertz/</guid>
      <description>The Gamma 40 Hertz app gives you access to a quick brain boost. Some recent research suggests that 40 hertz gamma brain waves decline with age and that reversing the decline can be helpful. This app stimulates 40 hertz gamma waves through light, sound, and touch.
Features:
Multimodal, individually adjustable intensity across sound, touch, and sight 40 hertz square wave audio tone 40 hertz haptic vibration 40 hertz visual signal using your device’s flash Now available on the App Store!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Um Detector</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/the-um-detector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:17:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/the-um-detector/</guid>
      <description>The Um Detector (iOS / iPadOS) Do you want to improve your speaking? Do find yourself yourself overusing filler words? This app will help you break the habit and speak more confidently.
The Um Detector listens for when you say any these words and/or phrases: “um,” “like,” and “you know.” When it detects a filler word being used, the word will flash red, and optionally, your device will vibrate.
The free version of this app allows you to use it for 5 minutes per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Alterscope</title>
      <link>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/the-alterscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:10:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alterscopesolutions.com/pages/the-alterscope/</guid>
      <description>The Alterscope (Oculus Go Virtual Reality) In this simulation, you begin by selecting a conversation partner. The conversation starts when you record a question or statement. You are then transported into the perspective of your conversation partner, where you can listen and respond to what was said. Continue the conversation through as many rounds a you like, swapping perspectives each time. You can even take on a completely new perspective by observing the conversation from a third person point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
